Shrinks items to fit in your pocket!

[h1]Description:[/h1]

The [b]Magical Pouch[/b] is a normal container that you can carry around.
Configurable size via the mod settings: 
- 4 slots (2x2) 
- 9 slots (3x3) 
- 16 slots (4x4) 
The recipe can be found on the Magic tab.
It is configurable via the mod settings. By default:  
- 1 x Rope 
- 15 x Spider Web 
- 5 x Purple Gem 

The [b]Icy Magical Pouch[/b] is a container that keeps food fresh.
Configurable size via the mod settings: 
- 4 slots (2x2)
- 9 slots (3x3)
- 16 slots (4x4)
Configurable perish factor:
- Default: exactly like an Icebox;
- 25% better than the Icebox;
- 50% better than the Icebox;
- 75% better than the Icebox;
- None: keeps food fresh forever;
The recipe can be found on the Magic tab.
It is configurable via the mod settings. By default:  
- 1 x Rope 
- 15 x Spider Web 
- 10 x Blue Gem 

In order to create either one of them, the player requires a Prestihatitator. 

Also available for [url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=399011777]Don't Starve and Reign of Giants[/url]. 

[h1]Changes:[/h1]

☑ made pouch-ception impossible;
☑ added option to change size to 9x9; 
☑ added option to change size to 2x2; 
☑ added options for customizing the recipe;
☑ added Icy Magical Pouch; it has it's own configurable settings;

[h1]Suggestions:[/h1]

☐ add some color (possibly configurable); currently working on it;

☐ add option to choose between accepting stackable items or not;

☒ add variable display position;
☒ [strike]add a special equip slot for the pouch AND/OR make the pouch unique-equipped[/strike];
☒ [strike]make it a drop from certain creatures with a customizable drop rate[/strike];

[h1]Compatibility issues:[/h1]

☑ Freezer: should be okay now; if not, please let me know;

[h1]Special thanks:[/h1]

Valve - for this amazing platform;
[url=http://store.steampowered.com/search/?developer=Klei%20Entertainment]Klei Entertainment[/url] - for this great game;
All the people that have contributed ideas or helped test this mod; 

[h1]Additional information:[/h1]

Feel free to post your questions or suggestions in the comment section below.
I am improving and updating this mod in my free time; so, please, bear with me.
If you like this mod, don't forget to rate it!
Have a great day!